[
    {
        "id": 792,
        "question": "What is Hypervisor?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "A hypervisor is a software that makes virtualization possible. It is also called Virtual Machine Monitor.",
            "answer_b": "A hypervisor is a hardware that makes optimization possible. It is also called Virtual Machine Monitor.",
            "answer_c": "A hypervisor is a software that makes optimization possible. It is also called Virtual Machine Monitor.",
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Docker"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Docker",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    },
    {
        "id": 179,
        "question": "Containers running on a single machine all share the same operating system kernel.",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "False",
            "answer_b": "True",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Docker"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Docker",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    },
    {
        "id": 849,
        "question": "How to remove the docker container with container id mentioned in the command.",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "$ docker rm -rf 9b6343d3b5a0",
            "answer_b": "$ docker -rm rf 9b6343d3b5a0",
            "answer_c": "$ docker rm 9b6343d3b5a0",
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Docker"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Docker",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    },
    {
        "id": 805,
        "question": "How to start a container?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "$ docker push <container_id>",
            "answer_b": "$ docker -->start <container_id>",
            "answer_c": "$ docker start <container_id>",
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Docker"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Docker",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    }, {
        "id": 875,
        "question": "If the Plesk server can't run Docker locally, you can still connect to a remote Docker server to manage containers. You'll need:",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "A virtuozzo 6 container",
            "answer_b": "One separate ready-to-code environment",
            "answer_c": "A Windows Server",
            "answer_d": "The Plesk Docker extension",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Docker"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Docker",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_d"
    }, {
        "id": 883,
        "question": "What is the difference between Docker image and layer.",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Docker image is created with a series of read-only layers and layer in docker represents instructions on the Dockerfile of the image.",
            "answer_b": "Docker image is created with a series of write-only layers and layer in docker represents instructions on the Dockerfile of the container.",
            "answer_c": null,
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Docker"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Docker",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 855,
        "question": "How to login into docker hub.",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "$ docker $login",
            "answer_b": "$ docker --log",
            "answer_c": "$ docker login",
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Docker"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Docker",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    }, {
        "id": 1026,
        "question": "What is Docker Swarm mode?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "A swarm is the name of the latest Docker release",
            "answer_b": "A swarm is a group of machines that are running Docker and joined into a cluster",
            "answer_c": "Docker swarm is also known as Docker Hub",
            "answer_d": "Docker swarm is a tool for managing your CI/CD pipelines",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Docker"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Docker",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 853,
        "question": "How to stop a docker container immediately?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "$ docker terminate",
            "answer_b": "$ docker kill",
            "answer_c": "$ docker stop",
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Docker"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Docker",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 864,
        "question": "How to create a volume which docker container will use to store data.",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "$ docker --volume create",
            "answer_b": "$ docker volume create",
            "answer_c": "$ docker create volume",
            "answer_d": null,
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "correct_answer": "answer_a",
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Docker"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Docker",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    }
]
